<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andrea&#39;s Blog on running mind</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Andrea&#39;s Blog on running mind</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>perspective</title>
      <link>/2019/10/06/perspective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/10/06/perspective/</guid>
      <description>Being human, as humans are wont to do, I sometimes get caught up in the drama of my own life. I assign it an importance in the grand scheme of things that is so overblown, so exaggerated as to be laughable. And it helps to be reminded of that, so you can laugh at your own folly.
I was listening to an audio book recently, I think it was The Practicing Mind by &amp;hellip; .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strava</title>
      <link>/2018/10/08/strava/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/08/strava/</guid>
      <description>## resource_state athlete.resource_state athlete.firstname athlete.lastname ## 1 2 2 Jody R. ## 2 2 2 Kristin M. ## 3 2 2 Andrew M. ## 4 2 2 Mike H. ## 5 2 2 Vicki Z. ## 6 2 2 Emily H. ## name ## 1 Lunch Run ## 2 Intervals today because tomorrow afternoon looks beautiful and I want to ride my bike ## 3 Lunch Run ## 4 Lunch Run ## 5 Hydrocut with Emily ## 6 Thanksgiving Morning Run ## distance moving_time elapsed_time total_elevation_gain type workout_type ## 1 7559.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>beer</title>
      <link>/favourites/beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/favourites/beer/</guid>
      <description>The mouth of a perfectly contented man is filled with beer. 
- Egyptian description, 2200 B.C. In progress&amp;hellip; a compendium of our favourite beers and the places to buy and consume them.
 The Boathouse, Kitchener ON A live music venue and restaurant in the heart of Kitchener at Victoria Park.  The Bent Elbow, Kitchener ON Abe Erb, Waterloo ON  Buggywhip | IPA | 6.3% ABV Imbibe Food/Drink, Kitchener ON  Specializing in craft beer, continuously rotate six beer taps with a wide variety of Ontario Craft Breweries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Posts about running and various other things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>quotations</title>
      <link>/favourites/quotations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/favourites/quotations/</guid>
      <description>The Eden Express, Mark Vonnegut  Among amateurs, most &amp;ldquo;touch-move&amp;rdquo; games are lost on stupid blunders. The game becomes pointless very early: neither player learns anything. I&amp;rsquo;m capable of playing a good game of touch-move, but I have a hard time enjoying it. I beat players I should lose to and lose to players I should beat. Either way, it leaves a bad taste in my mouth. Touch-move fans argue with equal fervor that being able to take moves back ruins the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whack-a-Mole</title>
      <link>/2016/03/22/whack-a-mole/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/03/22/whack-a-mole/</guid>
      <description>I’m starting to feel like one of those forlorn sailors from old-timey days, shipwrecked in some god-forsaken land without food, beginning to seriously contemplate cannibalism as their compatriots&amp;rsquo; limbs start to more closely resemble juicy chicken drumsticks than fleshy appendages.
Day 10: Still hurts. More elliptical. I wonder how difficult it would be to smash this thing? Where are those old golf clubs we have… But I jest - I truly don’t mind the elliptical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time</title>
      <link>/2016/03/13/time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/03/13/time/</guid>
      <description>&#34;How did it get so late so soon? It&#39;s night before it&#39;s afternoon. December is here before it&#39;s June. My goodness how the time has flewn. How did it get so late so soon?&#34; - Dr.Seuss  I love having short hair - it requires a mere 90 seconds of attention each morning and has reduced my shampoo consumption at least ten-fold. The only drawback is it requires more frequent haircuts - every 4-5 weeks if I’m to avoid that perpetually disheveled, unkempt look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ironman Muskoka Race Report</title>
      <link>/2015/09/07/ironman-muskoka-race-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/09/07/ironman-muskoka-race-report/</guid>
      <description>Poor blog, this must be how you feel after an entire summer of neglect. The writing and computer-y projects I was excited about before Boston have not been compatible with warm weather, ironman training, and a busier-than-usual summer at work. But shorter days are signaling the demise of summer, and I find myself in a 5-week limbo between Ironman Muskoka and the Chicago marathon - a good time to retool and attend to everything that has taken a backseat to training over the past four months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schrödinger&#39;s Stress Fracture</title>
      <link>/2015/04/03/schr%C3%B6dingers-stress-fracture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/04/03/schr%C3%B6dingers-stress-fracture/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s incredible what a week off from running can do. On the one hand I feel like I have so much energy I want to run 50 miles at marathon pace, while on the other my body seems to have forgotten all movement patterns associated with running. I used to experience this with swimming all the time - a couple of missed practices due to illness and my feel for the water vanished, at least for a day or two.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serious Juju</title>
      <link>/2015/03/21/serious-juju/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/21/serious-juju/</guid>
      <description>Without any coordination, big A and I started our runs at the same time down to the minute, and went the same distance down to a tenth of a mile. Clearly we possess some sort of supernatural marital running synchronicity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Over the Hump</title>
      <link>/2015/03/12/over-the-hump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/12/over-the-hump/</guid>
      <description>I felt a sense of relief on many fronts this week. Last week was my peak long run distance (24 miles), my highest volume of running ever, and my first time over 100 miles. It also marked the first break in winter, with some positively gorgeous weather on Sunday. I had two easy runs on the schedule, and sometimes that second one can be something of a drag when I really just feel like putting my feet up after a long run and a long training week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small Jobs</title>
      <link>/2015/03/02/small-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/02/small-jobs/</guid>
      <description>The first races in the local running series took place last weekend - the aptly named Re-Fridgee-Eighter 8 mile and 8 km races. These are fun, non-standard distances and I signed up for the 8 miler. This was the first race shorter than a half-marathon I&amp;rsquo;ve done in a while. To be honest I&amp;rsquo;m a little frightened of shorter races - I find the prospect of really hard running more daunting than the challenge of longer distances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rest</title>
      <link>/2015/02/23/rest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/02/23/rest/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Activity and rest are two vital aspects of life. To find a balance in them is a skill in itself. Wisdom is knowing when to have rest, when to have activity, and how much of each to have. Finding them in each other - activity in rest and rest in activity - is the ultimate freedom.” Sri Sri Ravi Shankar, Celebrating Silence: Excerpts from Five Years of Weekly Knowledge 1995-2000  I&amp;rsquo;m dealing with a little foot injury right now, and after a huge block of consistent training I struggled at first with having to take some time off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/other/club_segments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/other/club_segments/</guid>
      <description>.info { padding: 6px 8px; font: 14px/16px Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; background: white; background: rgba(255,255,255,0.8); box-shadow: 0 0 15px rgba(0,0,0,0.2); border-radius: 5px; } .info h4 { margin: 0 0 5px; color: #777; } .legend { line-height: 18px; color: #555; } .legend i { width: 18px; height: 18px; float: left; margin-right: 8px; opacity: 0.7; }   All 2k or more Less than 2k     var link_base = &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>coffee</title>
      <link>/favourites/coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/favourites/coffee/</guid>
      <description>A mathematician is a device for turning coffee into theorems 
- Alfréd Rényi In progress&amp;hellip; Great coffee shops and breakfast places we&amp;rsquo;ve visited locally and whilst traveling.
 A Matter of Taste, Kitchener ON The Yeti Cafe, Kitchener ON The Bauer Cafe, Waterloo ON Monigram Coffee Roasters, Cambridge ON Locomotive Espresso, London ON Fire Roasted Coffee, London ON Balzacs Coffee, Kitchener ON Revel Caffe, Stratford ON Anchored Ship Coffee Bar, Seattle WA The Wandering Goat, Eugene OR Trident Booksellers and Cafe, Boston MA The Friendly Toast, Cambridge MA Birch Coffee, New York Blue Bottle Coffee, New York Hideout Coffee House, Austin TX  Austin’s oldest independent coffee house.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>