<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andrea&#39;s Blog on running mind</title>
    <link>/favourites/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Andrea&#39;s Blog on running mind</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/favourites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>beer</title>
      <link>/favourites/beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/favourites/beer/</guid>
      <description>The mouth of a perfectly contented man is filled with beer. 
- Egyptian description, 2200 B.C. In progress&amp;hellip; a compendium of our favourite beers and the places to buy and consume them.
 The Boathouse, Kitchener ON A live music venue and restaurant in the heart of Kitchener at Victoria Park.  The Bent Elbow, Kitchener ON Abe Erb, Waterloo ON  Buggywhip | IPA | 6.3% ABV Imbibe Food/Drink, Kitchener ON  Specializing in craft beer, continuously rotate six beer taps with a wide variety of Ontario Craft Breweries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>quotations</title>
      <link>/favourites/quotations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/favourites/quotations/</guid>
      <description>The Eden Express, Mark Vonnegut  Among amateurs, most &amp;ldquo;touch-move&amp;rdquo; games are lost on stupid blunders. The game becomes pointless very early: neither player learns anything. I&amp;rsquo;m capable of playing a good game of touch-move, but I have a hard time enjoying it. I beat players I should lose to and lose to players I should beat. Either way, it leaves a bad taste in my mouth. Touch-move fans argue with equal fervor that being able to take moves back ruins the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>coffee</title>
      <link>/favourites/coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/favourites/coffee/</guid>
      <description>A mathematician is a device for turning coffee into theorems 
- Alfréd Rényi In progress&amp;hellip; Great coffee shops and breakfast places we&amp;rsquo;ve visited locally and whilst traveling.
 A Matter of Taste, Kitchener ON The Yeti Cafe, Kitchener ON The Bauer Cafe, Waterloo ON Monigram Coffee Roasters, Cambridge ON Locomotive Espresso, London ON Fire Roasted Coffee, London ON Balzacs Coffee, Kitchener ON Revel Caffe, Stratford ON Anchored Ship Coffee Bar, Seattle WA The Wandering Goat, Eugene OR Trident Booksellers and Cafe, Boston MA The Friendly Toast, Cambridge MA Birch Coffee, New York Blue Bottle Coffee, New York Hideout Coffee House, Austin TX  Austin’s oldest independent coffee house.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>